(Q1) SALLY: Good morning. Thanks for coming in to see us here at the agency, JOE. I'm one of the agency representatives, and my name's SALLY Baker. SALLY：
JOE: Hi SALLY. I think we spoke on the phone, didn't we? JOE：
SALLY: That's right, we did. So thank you for sending in your CV. We've had quite a careful look at it and I think we have two jobs that might be suitable for you. SALLY：
JOE: OK.
SALLY: The first one is in a company based in North London. They're looking for an administrative assistant. SALLY：
JOE: OK. What sort of company is it? JOE：
[Q1答案句] SALLY: They're called Home Solutions and they design and make furniture. SALLY：
JOE: Oh, I don't know much about that, but it sounds interesting. JOE：
(Q2) SALLY: Yes, well as I said, they want someone in their office, and looking at your past experience it does look as if you fit quite a few of the requirements. SALLY：
So on your CV it appears you've done some data entry?
JOE: Yes.
[Q2答案句] SALLY: So that's one skill they want. Then they expect the person they appoint to attend meetings and take notes there … SALLY：
JOE: OK. I've done that before, yes.
(Q3) SALLY: And you'd need to be able to cope with general admin. SALLY：
[Q3答案句] JOE: Filing, and keeping records and so on? That should be OK. And in my last job I also had to manage the diary. JOE：
SALLY: Excellent. That's something they want here too. I'd suggest you add it to your CV – SALLY：
I don't think you mentioned that, did you?
JOE: No.
(Q4) SALLY: So as far as the requirements go, they want good computer skills, of course, and they particularly mention spreadsheets. SALLY：
JOE: That should be fine.
SALLY: And interpersonal skills – which would be something they'd check with your references. SALLY：
JOE: I think that should be OK, yes.
[Q4答案句] SALLY: Then they mention that they want someone who is careful and takes care with details – just looking at your CV, I'd say you're probably alright there. SALLY：
(Q5) JOE: I think so, yes. Do they want any special experience? JOE：
SALLY: I think they wanted some experience of teleconferencing. SALLY：
JOE: I've got three years' experience of that. JOE：
[Q5答案句] SALLY: Let's see, yes, good. In fact they're only asking for at least one year, so that's great. So is that something that might interest you? SALLY：
JOE: It is, yes. The only thing is, you said they were in North London so it would be quite a long commute for me. JOE：
SALLY: OK.
(Q6) SALLY: So the second position might suit you better as far as the location goes; that's for a warehouse assistant and that's in South London. SALLY：
JOE: Yes, that would be a lot closer. JOE：
SALLY: And you've worked in a warehouse before, haven't you? SALLY：
JOE: Yes.
[Q6答案句] SALLY: So as far as the responsibilities for this position go, they want someone who can manage the stock, obviously, and also deliveries. SALLY：
JOE: That should be OK. You've got to keep track of stuff, but I've always been quite good with numbers. JOE：
(Q7) SALLY: Good. that's their first requirement. And they want someone who's computer literate, which we know you are. SALLY：
JOE: Sure.
SALLY: Then they mention organisational skills. They want someone who's well organised. SALLY：
JOE: Yes, I think I am.
[Q7答案句+确认] SALLY: And tidy?
JOE: Yes, they go together really, don't they?
(Q8) SALLY: Sure. Then the usual stuff; they want someone who can communicate well both orally and in writing. SALLY：
JOE: OK. And for the last warehouse job I had, one of the things I enjoyed most was being part of a team. JOE：
I found that was really essential for the job.
[Q8答案句（代词指代）] SALLY: Excellent. Yes, they do mention that they want someone who's used to that, yes.
(Q9) Now when you were working in a warehouse last time, what sorts of items were you dealing with?
JOE: It was mostly bathroom and kitchen equipment, sinks and stoves and fridges. JOE：
[Q9答案句] SALLY: So you're OK moving heavy things? SALLY：
JOE: Sure. I'm quite strong, and I've had the training. JOE：
(Q10) SALLY: Good. Now as far as experience goes, they mention they want someone with a licence, and that you have experience of driving in London – SALLY：
so you can cope with the traffic and so on.
JOE: Yes, no problem.
[Q10答案句] SALLY: And you've got experience of warehouse work … and the final thing they mention is customer service. I think looking at your CV you're OK there. SALLY：
JOE: Right. So what about pay? Can you tell me a bit more about that, please … JOE：